Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- M, 300693
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing (New York, NY) I, 1961-1965; 300741 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing (New York, NY) II, 1961-1965; 300742 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing (New York, NY), 1966-1969; 300743 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing (New York, NY) I, 1970; 300744 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing (New York, NY), 1971-; 300745 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing (New York, NY), undated; 300746 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Music School, 1947-1951; 324814 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Student Strike Committee (New York, NY), undated; 300747 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Urban Training Facility (MUST) (New York, NY), 1967; 300748 (Box 58)
  - Mezhdunarodnaya Kniga, 1959; 437206 (Box 58)
  - Miami Conventions Coalition, 1972; 300749 (Box 58)
  - Michael Forde Bookshop, 1972; 300750 (Box 58)
  - Michael Stephens Bookseller (Berkeley, CA), 1982-; 300751 (Box 58)
  - Michigan Free Speech Defense Committee, 1965; 373917 (Box 58)
  - Michigan State University: Labor and Industrial Relations Center, 1962; 300752 (Box 58)
  - Michigan Worker, undated; 437203 (Box 58)
  - Microcosm Publishing, 2010; 423080 (Box 58)
  - Middle East Institute, 324816 (Box 58)
  - Middle East Peace Network, 1988-; 324817 (Box 58)
  - Middle East Research and Information Project, 1972-, 2002; 300753 (Box 58)
  - Midland Cooperative Wholesale (Minneapolis, MN), 1946-1947; 300754 (Box 58)
  - Midland Iron and Steel Wages Board, The, 1923; 433916 (Box 58)
  - Midnight Special Law Collective (zine), undated; 324818 (Box 58)
  - Mid-Peninsula Christian Ministry (East Palo Alto, CA), 1968; 300755 (Box 58)
  - Midstream, 1966; 373013 (Box 58)
  - Midwest Academy (Chicago, IL), 1973; 300756 (Box 58)
  - Midwest Center for Labor Research, 1983-; 300757 (Box 58)
  - Midwest Committee for Protection of Foreign Born (Chicago, IL), 1948-1950; 300758 (Box 58)
  - Midwest Conference: Voluntary Organizations and a World Without War, 1965; 300759 (Box 58)
  - Midwest Farmer-Labor Alliance, undated; 324819 (Box 58)
  - Mid-West Youth Congress (St. Paul, MN), 1935; 300760 (Box 58)
  - Migrant Children's Fund, 195-1961; 300761 (Box 58)
  - Militant Action Caucus, 1970s; 300762 (Box 58)
  - Militant Socialist International: British Section, 1939-1941; 300872 (Box 58)
  - Military Families Support Network (Persian Gulf), 1990; 324820 (Box 58)
  - Military Legal Center, undated; 373860 (Box 58)
  - Million Worker March, 2004; 373014 (Box 58)
  - Millions for Mumia (New York), 1999-; 300763 (Box 58)
  - Milton Tonwsite Colony (Milton, OK), 1913; 300764 (Box 58)
  - Milk Research Council, 1936-1937; 300765 (Box 58)
  - Milwaukee Alliance (integration), undated; 324821 (Box 58)
  - Milwaukee Graduate Assistants' Association, 2011; 422952 (Box 58)
  - Milwaukee Peace Action Center, 1972; 300766 (Box 58)
  - Milwaukee Rank and File Action Committee, 1966; 300767 (Box 58)
  - Mine of Information - Archives (Swansea, Wales), undated; 300768 (Box 58)
  - Mines for the Nation Committee, 1920; 300769 (Box 58)
  - Ministerio de Propaganda (Spain) (Ayuda a Madrid, pamphlet), 1937; 324825 (Box 58)
  - Minneapolis Community Union Project, undated; 324829 (Box 58)
  - Minnesota Association of Cooperatives, 1946; 300770 (Box 58)
  - Minnesota Committee for Wallace, 1948; 300771 (Box 58)
  - Minnesota Connections, 1972; 300772 (Box 58)
  - Minnesota Farmer-Labor Association, 1941; 300773 (Box 58)
  - Minnesota Iron Range Strikers Defense Committee, 1916; 300774 (Box 58)
  - Minnesota Libertarian Society, undated; 300775 (Box 58)
  - Minnesota Prisoners Union: Women Prisoners Union, 1975; 300776 (Box 58)
  - Minority of One (American Alternative dedicated to the Eradication of all Restrictions on Thoughts), 1961-1965; 300777 (Box 58)
  - Mississippi Economic Advancement Task-Force (MEAT), 1964; 300785 (Box 58)
  - Mississippi Free Press, undated; 300778 (Box 58)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party I, 1964-1965; 300779 (Box 59)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party II, 1964-1969; 300780 (Box 59)
  - Mississippi Freedom Labor Union, 1965; 300781 (Box 59)
  - Mississippi Freedom School Teachers, 1964; 300782 (Box 59)
  - Mississippi Project Parents Committee, 1964; 300783 (Box 59)
  - Misled Youth, 2007-; 300784 (Box 59)
  - Mobilization Direct Action Project, 1967; 373941 (Box 59)
  - Mobilization for Global Justice, 2000-2002; 300786 (Box 59)
  - Mobilization for Justice and Peace in Central America and Southern Africa, 1987; 380091 (Box 59)
  - Mobilization for Survival, 1981-, undated; 300787 (Box 59)
  - Mobilize New York, undated; 300788 (Box 59)
  - Mooney Defense Committee, 1930; 437202 (Box 59)
  - Modern Book and News Company (booklist), undated; 300789 (Box 59)
  - Modern Language Association (MLA): Commission on the Status of Women in the Profession, 1969; 300790 (Box 59)
  - Modern Publishers (Indore, India) (Libertarian Book House), 1946-1947; 300791 (Box 59)
  - Modern School (Salt Lake City, UT), 1910; 324851 (Box 59)
  - Modern School (Stelton, NJ) I, 1940-; 300792 (Box 59)
  - Modern School (Stelton, NJ) II, 1940-, undated; 300793 (Box 59)
  - Modern Times Theatre, undated; 300797 (Box 59)
  - Mohegan Modern School (Crompond, NY), 1938-; 300798 (Box 59)
  - Mohrenklub, circa 1870s; 300799 (Box 59)
  - Monkey Wrench Books, undated; 300794 (Box 59)
  - Monroe Defense Committee, 1961; 300795 (Box 59)
  - Montreal Council to Aid War Resistors, 1969; 300796 (Box 59)
  - Mon Valley Unemployed Committee (Pennsylvania), 1988; 300800 (Box 59)
  - Monthly Review Press I, 1950-; 300801 (Box 59)
  - Monthly Review Press II, 1950-; 300802 (Box 59)
  - Monthly Review Press III, 1950-; 300803 (Box 59)
  - Monthly Review Press IV, 1950-; 300804 (Box 59)
  - More Gardens! Coalition, undated; 324837 (Box 59)
  - More to Come, undated; 327923 (Box 59)
  - Morning Freiheit (New York, NY), 1944-1965, undated; 301022 (Box 59)
  - Morning Star, undated; 373016 (Box 59)
  - Moscow Trials Campaign Committee, 1990; 324838 (Box 59)
  - Moslem Students Society (Long Beach, CA), 1981; 301023 (Box 59)
  - Mother Earth Books (Seattle, WA), 1981, undated; 301024 (Box 59)
  - Mother Jones (San Francisco, CA) (serial), 1982-; 301025 (Box 59)
  - Mother Rocco's, 1963; 334766 (Box 59)
  - Mothers Committee for Peace and Freedom (Denver, CO), undated; 301026 (Box 59)
  - Mother's Crusade for Victory Over Communism (Mesa, AZ), 1966; 301027 (Box 59)
  - Motor City Consumers Cooperative (Detroit, MI), undated; 301028 (Box 59)
  - Motor City Labor League and the Alliance (Detroit, MI), 1972-1973; 301029 (Box 59)
  - Motsu Project, 1973; 374226 (Box 59)
  - Mount Sinai Committee for Human Rights, undated; 301030 (Box 59)
  - Mouvement Haitien de Liberation (East White Plains, NY), 1978; 301031 (Box 59)
  - Move, 1976; 324842 (Box 59)
  - Movement for a Democratic Society, 1969, undated; 324843 (Box 59)
  - Movement for a New Society, 1976-1980; 301032 (Box 59)
  - Movement for Economic Justice, 1970s; 301033 (Box 59)
  - Movement Liberation Front (San Francisco, CA), circa 1970s; 301034 (Box 60)
  - Movement of the Libertarian Left, undated; 423058 (Box 60)
  - Movement of the Revolutionary Left (Movimiento de Izquierida Revolucionaria) (Chile), 1977; 301035 (Box 60)
  - Movement Speakers Bureau, undated; 301036 (Box 60)
  - Moveon.org, 2002-; 324858 (Box 60)
  - Movimento Popular de Libertacao de Angola, 1969; 301037 (Box 60)
  - Movimiento Liberacion Nacional (Argentina), 1967-1968; 301038 (Box 60)
  - Movimiento Pro Independencia de Puerto Rico, 1960-1971; 301039 (Box 60)
  - Movimiento Socialista Popular (Puerto Rico), circa 1975; 301040 (Box 60)
  - Movimiento Unidad Revolucionaria, undated; 301041 (Box 60)
  - Mrs. Yank W.I.V.E.S Newsletter, 1944-1945; 324859 (Box 60)
  - Mulberry Community House (New York, NY), 324860 (Box 60)
  - Museum of American Labor (Washington, DC), undated; 301042 (Box 60)
  - Musicians Socialist Club of New York, undated; 301043 (Box 60)
  - Mutual Redevelopment Houses (New York, NY) (Penn South), 1978, undated; 301044 (Box 60)
  - Mutual Support Network, undated; 301045 (Box 60)
  - Mutualist Associates (Los Angeles, CA), undated; 301046 (Box 60)
  - Muzei Revoliutsii (Russia), undated; 301047 (Box 60)
- N, 301048
  - Nader 2000 (campaign), 301049 (Box 60)
  - NAFTA Not a Fair Trade for All (exhibition), 2001; 301050 (Box 60)
  - Naim Frasheri Publishing House (Tirana, Albania), 1963-1966; 380092 (Box 60)
  - Nation, The, 1966; 373693 (Box 60)
  - National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League: New York, 2002-; 301051 (Box 60)
  - National Abortion Rights Action League, undated; 380093 (Box 60)
  - National Academic Freedom Committee, 1938; 301052 (Box 60)
  - National Action Network, 2001-; 324871 (Box 60)
  - National Action/Research on the Military-Industrial Complex, 1971-1978; 301053 (Box 60)
  - National Administrative Committee, 1969; 374333 (Box 60)
  - National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor I, 1959-1967; 301054 (Box 60)
  - National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor II, 1959-1967; 301055 (Box 60)
  - National Afro-American Labor Council, 1970-1972; 301056 (Box 60)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression, 1973-1975, 1978-1983, undated; 301057 (Box 60)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression, 1990-1996; 324872 (Box 60)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression: Certificate of Incorporation, 1974; 324873 (Box 60)
  - National Alliance of Russian Soldiers (Narodno-Trudovoi Soiuz), 1961; 301058 (Box 60)
  - National Alternative Politics Conference, 1989; 301059 (Box 60)
  - National American Women Suffrage Association, 1910-1912, undated; 301060 (Box 60)
  - National American Suffrage Association, 1911; 301061 (Box 60)
  - National Anti-Drug Coalition, 1979-1980; 301062 (Box 60)
  - National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation (New York, NY), 1955, 1975-1983; 327943 (Box 60)
  - National Anti-Injunction League, 1911; 301063 (Box 60)
  - National Anti-Racist Organizing Committee, 1981; 324874 (Box 60)
  - National Anti-War Congress, 1938-1941; 301064 (Box 60)
  - National Assembly for Democratic Rights, 1961-1962; 301065 (Box 60)
  - National Assembly of Women (Great Britain), circa 1952; 301075 (Box 60)
  - National Assembly to Stop Plant Closings and Fight for Jobs (Chicago, IL), 1987-; 301076 (Box 60)
  - National Association for Child Development, 1924-1925; 301077 (Box 60)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1919-1958; 301066 (Box 60)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1959-1964; 324875 (Box 60)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1965-1976; 324876 (Box 60)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund, 1943, 1960s; 301067 (Box 60)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP): Labor Department, 1991-; 301068 (Box 60)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP): Operation Mississippi, 1964; 301069 (Box 60)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP): Pamphlets and Publications, 1918, 1940-1949; 301070 (Box 60)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP): Pamphlets and Publications I, 1950-1959; 301071 (Box 61)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP): Pamphlets and Publications II, 1950-1959; 301072 (Box 61)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP): Pamphlets and Publications, 1955-; 324884 (Box 61)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP): Pamphlets and Publications, 1960-1969; 301073 (Box 61)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP): Pamphlets and Publications, undated; 301074 (Box 61)
  - National Association for the Legal Support of Alternative Schools (Santa Fe, NM), 1978; 301078 (Box 61)
  - National Association of 9 to 5 Working Women, 1987-; 324885 (Box 61)
  - National Association of Arab Americans, undated; 373019 (Box 61)
  - National Association of Cotton Manufacturers, 1917; 327944 (Box 61)
  - National Association of Manufacturers I, 1912-1956; 301079 (Box 61)
  - National Association of Manufacturers II, 1912-1956; 301080 (Box 61)
  - National Association of Manufacturers III, 1912-1956; 301081 (Box 61)
  - National Association of Manufacturers IV, 1912-1956; 324886 (Box 61)
  - National Black Coalition for 1984, 327945 (Box 61)
  - National Black Draft Counselors, 1971; 327946 (Box 61)
  - National Black Human Rights Coalition, 1979; 327947 (Box 61)
  - National Black Independent Political Party I, 1980-1981; 301082 (Box 61)
  - National Black Independent Political Party II, 1980-1981; 301193 (Box 61)
  - National Black Labor Congress (Newark, NJ), 1968; 301083 (Box 61)
  - National Black United Front, 1981; 301194 (Box 61)
  - National Boycott Gimbels and Saks Coordinating Committee, 1970; 301084 (Box 61)
  - National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East, 1991-; 324887 (Box 61)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees, undated; 374748 (Box 61)
  - National Center for Employee Ownership, 1982; 301085 (Box 61)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1974; 301086 (Box 61)
  - National Center for Trade Union Action and Democracy, undated; 375404 (Box 61)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1926-1944, undated; 301087 (Box 61)
  - National Child Labor Committee I (also OV), 1905-1951; 301088 (Box 61)
  - National Child Labor Committee II, 1905-1951; 301089 (Box 61)
  - National Child Labor Committee: National Committee on the Education of Migrant Children, 1973; 301090 (Box 61)
  - National Chile Center (New York, NY), 1976-1977; 301091 (Box 61)
  - National Circulating Library of Original Peace Posters (Philadelphia, PA), undated; 301092 (Box 61)
  - National Citizens Committee for Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Holiday, 1971; 301093 (Box 61)
  - National Citizens' Committee for the Protection of Civil Rights in the Automobile Industry, 1937; 301094 (Box 61)
  - National Citizens Committee to Defend Academic Freedom at St. Johns University (New York), undated; 301095 (Box 61)
  - National Citizens' New Year's Eve Peace Observance, undated; 373954 (Box 61)
  - National Citizens Political Action Committee, 1944-1946, undated; 301096 (Box 61)
  - National Civic Federation, 1913-1934; 301097 (Box 61)
  - National Civil Liberties Bureau I, 1917-; 301098 (Box 61)
  - National Civil Liberties Bureau II, 1917-; 301099 (Box 62)
  - National Civil Rights Legislative Conference, 1949; 324915 (Box 62)
  - National Civil Service Reform League, 1912; 334779 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition Against Censorship, 2011; 422962 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition Against War, Racism, and Repression, 1970-1973; 301100 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1987-; 347650 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition to Fight Inflation and Unemployment, 1975; 326704 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition to Sign the Treaty Now!, 1973; 374172 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition to Stop the Rock, undated; 324925 (Box 62)
  - National Colombia Mobilization, 2003; 373020 (Box 62)
  - National Commission for the Defense of Democracy through Education (Washington, DC), undated; 324926 (Box 62)
  - National Commission on Working Women, 1978-1984; 301101 (Box 62)
  - National Committee Against Censorship of the Theater Arts, 1935; 301102 (Box 62)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, 1951-1971, undated; 301103 (Box 62)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation, 1973, 1989; 301104 (Box 62)
  - National Committee Against the Treaty of Moscow, 1960s; 324927 (Box 62)
  - National Committee: Continental Congress, circa 1933; 324928 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for a Fair Minimum Wage, 1945; 301105 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for a Free Europe: Pamphlets, 1948-1951; 301106 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for a Political Settlement in Vietnam, undated; 373677 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, undated; 437201 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress, undated; 327948 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Defense of Political Prisoners, 1936; 327949 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Full Employment, undated; 324929 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Indendent Political Action (NCIPA), 1988-1989; 324930 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Labor Israel, 1956-1957; 301109 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Peoples Rights, 1941; 301110 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Repeal of the McCarran Act, 1964-1965; 301111 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Rural Schools, 1960; 301112 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Student Mobilization for Peace, 1935; 301113 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Albany Defendants (Georgia), 1964; 301114 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Defense of Civil Rights in Tampa, undated; 334781 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Defense of Joanne Chesimard and Clark Souire, 1973-1974; 301115 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners, 1937, undated; 301116 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners, 1974-1975; 301117 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Extension of Labor Education, 1948-1950; 301118 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the New Party (Ottawa, Canada), 1961; 301119 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Student Congress Against War (New York, NY), undated; 301120 (Box 62)
  - National Committee of Unemployed Councils, 1930s; 301121 (Box 62)
  - National Committee of Yugoslavia for the Defense of Peace, 1950; 301122 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on Atomic Information, 1947; 301123 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on Employment of Youth, undated; 301124 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on Labor Injunctions, 1938; 301125 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor, 1922; 301126 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on the Churches and World Peace, 1930; 301127 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee I, 1961-1969; 301128 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee II, 1961-1969; 301129 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee III, 1961-1969; 325712 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Abolish the Poll Tax, 1943-1945; 301130 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defeat the Mundt Bill (Washington, DC), undated; 301131 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defend and Support Johnny Coward and Bartee Haile, circa 1970; 301132 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defend Negro Leadership, 1954; 327958 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defend New Afrikan Freedom Fighters, undated; 324931 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defend the Bakke Decision, circa 1977; 324932 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Free the Five (Cuba), undated; 373021 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case, 1976-; 326705 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Repeal the McCarran Act, undated; 324933 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Secure Justice in the Rosenberg-Sobell Case, undated; 373023 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Uphold Constitutional Government, undated; 324934 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Win Amnesty for Smith Act Victims (New York, NY), 1954-1955; 301133 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Win the Peace (Washington, DC), 1946; 301134 (Box 62)
  - National Conference for New Politics, 1967-1968, undated; 301135 (Box 62)
  - National Conference of American Socialists, 1958; 327959 (Box 62)
  - National Conference of Charities and Collections, Proceedings (Boston, MA), Jun 1911; 304318 (Box 62)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (New York, NY), 1943-1954, undated; 301136 (Box 62)
  - National Conference of Labor, Socialist and Radical Movements (New York, NY), 1918; 301137 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Fundamental Problems in the Education of Negroes (Washington, DC), 1934; 301138 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Lynching (New York, NY), 1919; 301139 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Organized Resistance, 2001-; 324935 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Public Service Employment (New York, NY), 1971-1973; 301140 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Soviet Jewry, undated; 422929 (Box 62)
  - National Conference of Synagogue Youth, undated; 423128 (Box 62)
  - National Congress for Puerto Rican Rights, 1987; 373024 (Box 63)
  - National Congress of Employees (Piermont, NY), 1985-1986; 301141 (Box 63)
  - National Congress of Neighborhood Women (New York, NY), circa 1970s; 324943 (Box 63)
  - National Congress of Unemployed Organizations (Chicago, IL), circa 1984; 301142 (Box 63)
  - National Consumers' League, 1911-1928; 301143 (Box 63)
  - National Consumers' League, 1929-1934; 301144 (Box 63)
  - National Consumers' League, 1935-1965; 301145 (Box 63)
  - National Consumers' League, undated; 301146 (Box 63)
  - National Coordinating Center in Solidarity with Chile, 1975-1976; 301147 (Box 63)
  - National Co-operative Men's Guild (Great Britain), 1924; 301148 (Box 63)
  - National Co-operative Society, undated; 301149 (Box 63)
  - National Cooperatives, Inc. I, 1939-1947; 301150 (Box 63)
  - National Cooperatives, Inc. II, 1939-1947; 324968 (Box 63)
  - National Coordinating Center in Solidarity with Chile, 1976; 375405 (Box 63)
  - National Coordinating Committee for Trade Union Action and Democracy, 1971-; 304499 (Box 63)
  - National Coordinating Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1965-1966; 301151 (Box 63)
  - National Council Against Conscription (Washington, DC), 1947-1954, undated; 301152 (Box 63)
  - National Council for American Education (New York, NY), 1952; 301153 (Box 63)
  - National Council for a Permanent Fair Employment Practice Committee (Washington, DC), 1944-1947; 301154 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Civil Liberties (Great Britain), 1922-1984; 301155 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Democratic Aid (Great Britain), undated; 301156 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Democratic Rights (Toronto, Canada), undated; 301157 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Industrial Peace (Washington, DC), 1960, undated; 301158 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Peace and Against Nuclear Weapons (Japan), undated; 301159 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Prevention of War, 1923-1941, undated; 301160 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Protection of Foreign Born Workers (New York, NY), undated; 301161 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Social Democracy, 1939; 301162 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Universal and Unconditional Amnesty (New York, NY) (see also OV box), 1976; 301163 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship I, 1943-; 301164 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship II, 1943-; 301165 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship III, 1943-; 301166 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Committee of Women, 1949; 301176 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets I, 1940-1949; 301167 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets II, 1940-1949; 301168 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets III, 1940-1949; 301169 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets IV, 1940-1949; 324994 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets I, 1950-1959; 301170 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets II, 1950-1959; 301171 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets III, 1950-1959; 324995 (Box 64)